http://www.imancosmetics.com/pages/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Notice - IMAN COSMETICS, INC.
Effective April 30, 2015
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
DISCLAIMER
Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the IMAN Cosmetics website. On some pages, you can make requests, and request to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Service or need requested
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself to respond to your request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to fulfill your request.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
To better serve your shopping experience, we may use third party web analytics services on this site, our social media platforms, or mobile applications, such as Google Analytics. The service providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use the site to better improve our business. To disable the Google Analytics cookie and any other third party web analytics service provider cookies, some browsers indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
Opt Out of Communications
If at any time you wish to opt-out of receiving e-mail updates or any other online communications that you have previously requested, simply click the “opt-out” feature within your IMAN Cosmetics email or send an e-mail to info@imancosmetics.com with the words "Remove from email list" in the subject line.
Link to Other sites:
Please note in certain pages, IMANCOSMETICS.com contains links to other sites that may not follow the same privacy policy as IMANCOSMETICS.com. For example, clicking on a link from one of our media partners or corporate partners will take you to an entirely different site. These sites may use cookies, collect data and/or use the data in ways that IMANCOSMETICS.com would not. IMAN COSMETICS AND IMPALA, INC ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS ON THESE OTHER SITES.
Social Media Disclaimer:
The views and opinions expressed on our social media sites from third parties do not represent IMAN Cosmetics, its employees or affiliates, therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the accuracy or reliability of information posted by external parties. IMAN Cosmetics material on this site may not be reproduced, distributed, transmitted, cached or otherwise used except with prior written permission of IMPALA, Inc. Copyright ©2015 IMPALA, Inc LLC IMAN Cosmetics. All worldwide rights reserved.
COPYRIGHT NOTICE
All text, images, and software code on this website are copyright property of IMPALA, Inc unless otherwise noted. It may be used for the personal education of site visitors, and may not be placed in the public domain. Any commercial reproduction, redistribution, publication, or other use by electronic means or otherwise is prohibited unless pursuant to a written license signed by the organization.
DISCLAIMER
The material in this site could include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. IMPALA, Inc may make changes or improvements at any time. The materials in this site are provided AS IS and without warranties of any kind either expressed or implied, to the fullest extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, IMPALA, Inc disclaims all warranties or merchantability for a particular purpose. IMPALA, Inc does not warrant that the functions contained in the material will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that this site or the server that makes it available are free of viruses or other harmful components. IMPALA, Inc does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use of or the result of the use of the material in this site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise.
IMPALA, Inc reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of the IMAN COSMETICS website constitutes consent to any policy then in effect.
